<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:segment="https://github.com/Viral-MediaLab/superglue-rss" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CSPAN1</title>
    <link>https://www.c-span.org/networks/?channel=c-span</link>
    <description>CSPAN1</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 20:14:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Journal</title>
      <link>http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480676452094.fc230aa2-1de7-4988-b2fa-b6f7e7363854.mp4#t=0.00,1125.96</link>
      <description>ROOM -- WE CAN PUT THAT BACK.
WE CAN PUT ANYTHING THE AMERICAN PUBLIC WANTS.
SO LONG AS YOU KNOW WASHINGTON WILL HAVE TO THE RAISE THAT
BACK UP. SO THIS IS YOUR POSTCARD NOT
OURS. THAT'S WHY WE'RE LISTENING SO
INTENTLY RIGHT NOW ON THE TAX REFORM PROPOSAL THAT WE'VE LAID
OUT. SO THAT'S HOW WE GO ALL IN FOR
FAIRNESS AND SIMPLICITY. THEN THE FINAL FORM IS BECAUSE
A FAIR AND SIMPLER TAX CODE DEMANDS A FAIR AND SIMPLER TAX
COLLECTER. IN THE IRS TODAY, IS A HUGE
AGENCY WITH THE POWER TO DESTROY LIVES AND BUSINESSES.
AND IT IS TARGETING AMERICANS BASED UPON THEIR POLITICAL
BELIEFS. THAT'S NOT ACCEPTABLE. SO WE PROPOSE TO BUST IT UP.
REDESIGN IT IN THREE, MUCH SMALLER, MUCH FOCUSED UNIT.
FOCUSED ON BUSINESS WITH TAX EXPERTS ON BUSINESS TO
ACCURATELY AND QUICKLY ANSWER BUSINESS QUESTIONS AND RESOLVE
DISPUTES FOR OUR BUSINESSES, LARGE OR SMALL. ANOTHER UNIT TO
DO THE SAME FOR FAMILIES. FOCUS ON CUSTOMER SERVICE. I DON'T
KNOW HOW MANY TRIED TO CALL THE IRS LATELY, BUT YOU DIDN'T GET
THROUGH. IF YOU SPOKE TO THREE PEOPLE, YOU GOT THREE DIFFERENT
ANSWERS WITH YOUR TAX QUESTION. THAT LEVEL OF CUSTOMER SERVICE
OR LACK OF IT, THAT'S NOT ACCEPTABLE IN YOUR
ORGANIZATION, IT'S NOT ACCEPTABLE IN THAT AGENCY. WE
PROPOSE CUSTOMER SERVICE, TIMELY ACCURATE ANSWERS TO OUR
TAX QUESTIONS. FINALLY, BECAUSE I'VE GROWN SO TIRED IN MY HOME,
I DIDN'T MOVE TO WASHINGTON, I LIVE IN THE COMMUNITY THE
WOODLANDS JUST NORTH OF HOUSTON AND FOR YEARS I HAVE HEARD FROM
FAMILIES AND SMALL BUSINESSES. THEY GET IN A TAX DISPUTE IN
THE IRS. SOMETIMES A RELATIVELY MINOR ONE. THEY WILL SPEND
YEARS AND YEARS, THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS. EVEN WHEN THEY WIN,
THEY'VE LOST. SO WE'RE PROPOSING A SMALL UNIT
INDEPENDENT OF TREASURING THE IRS LIKE SMALL CLAIMS COURT SO
AMERICANS CAN GET DISPUTES HEARD AND RESOLVED WITHOUT
HAVING TO SPEND THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS ON ATTORNEYS AND
ACCOUNTANTS. THAT'S HOW WE PROPOSE TO REDESIGN THE IRS IN
THE 21ST AGENCY WITH A SINGULAR MISSION OF CUSTOMER SERVICE. SO
AS YOU LOOK AT THOSE THREE PROPOSALS, YOU MAY BE THINKING,
THIS SOUNDS TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE, BUT IT'S NOT. WE'VE
DESIGNED THIS TO BREAK EVEN WITHIN THE BUDGET, CONSIDERING
THE ECONOMIC GROWTH THAT WILL COME WITH IT. IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO DO THAT, THE ONLY WAY TO LOWER RATES FOR EVERYBODY IS TO
ELIMINATE THE HUNDREDS OF SPECIAL TAX PROVISIONS FOR
SOME. SO THAT'S WHAT WE'RE PROPOSING TO YOU, SIGNIFICANT
TRADE-OFFS TO MOVE TO THIS. FOR EXAMPLE, IN BUSINESS, WE'RE
PROPOSING NOT TO DUCT YOUR NET INTEREST COSTS. IT IS A CHANGE
FROM WHERE WE ARE TODAY. THERE'S GOOD POLICY REASONS FOR
DOING THAT. ALLOWING FULL EXPENSING WHERE WE WRITE OFF
THINGS IMMEDIATELY THE FIRST YEAR AND CARRY THAT FORWARD. IF
YOU'RE BORROWING TO DO THAT AND WRITING OFF THAT INTEREST, THIS
POINT WE'RE GIVING YOU A NEGATIVE INTEREST RATE. WE ARE
PAYING YOU TO BUY STUFF. WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
ELIMINATING THAT AS WELL ALLOWS US TO GO TO A DRAMATICALLY MORE
PRO-GROWTH TAX GROWTH OVERALL. THAT'S A BIG CHANGE FROM WHAT
WE DO TODAY. WHICH IS WHY WE ARE ASKING BUSINESSES LARGE AND
SMALL TO TEST DRIVE THIS NEW BLUEPRINT INCLUDING THOSE
TRADE-OFFS. TO GIVE US FEEDBACK AS WE WORK TO IMPROVE THIS AT
EVERY STEP. FOR FAMILIES AND INDIVIDUALS, FOR EXAMPLE, SO
THERE ARE HUNDREDS OF PROVISIONS. IN OUR CASE WE
ADOPTED OUR TWO BOYS. IT'S THE BIGGEST BLESSING WE COULD HAVE.
WE DIDN'T TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE TAX CREDIT. BUT THAT'S
IMPORTANT TO PEOPLE. WHAT WE ARE PROPOSING TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE, RATHER THAN HAVE HUNDREDS OF THOSE PROVISIONS
THAT APPLY TO SOME AT SOME POINT IN THEIR LIFE WHY DON'T
WE LOWER THE TAX RATES FOR EVERYBODY. AMERICANS USE THOSE
DOLLARS FOR THE PRIORITIES IN THEIR LIFE. THAT'S A CHANGE
FROM WHERE WE'RE AT TODAY. ANOTHER. WE PROPOSE FOR THOSE
AMERICANSWHO ITEMIZE, THAT WE DON'T DUCT
THE STATE AND LOCAL INCOME SALES AND PROPERTY TAXES, WHICH
IS A BIG CHANGE FROM WHERE WE'RE AT TODAY. WE KEEP YOUR
TAXES HIGH. YOU SEND YOUR MONEY TO WASHINGTON. YOU HOPE YOU CAN
CLAW SOME OF IT BACK TO OFFSET LOCAL TAXES. WHAT'S GOING ON,
EVERYONE IS SUBSIDIZING EACH OTHER. MIDDLE CLASS TAXPAYERS
ARE SUBSIDIZING HIGHER EARNERS. LOW TAX COMMUNITIES AND STATES
ARE SUBSIDIZING HIGH TAX COMMUNITIES AND STATES. OUR
PROPOSAL IS THIS. RATHER THAN HIGH TAX AND EVERYONE SUBSIDIZE
EACH OTHER, WHY NOT LOWER THE TAXES AND EVERYONE PAY THEIR
OWN? THE ADDED BENEFIT IS THE FEDERAL TAX CODE WILL NO LONGER
SUBSIDIZE HIGHER TAXES AT THE LOCAL LEVEL. WE THINK THAT'S
MIRROR TO THAT. THAT IS A BIG CHANGE FROM WHERE WE ARE AT
TODAY. THAT'S WHY WE ARE ASKING THE AMERICAN PEOPLE TO CONSIDER
THE POST CARD, LOOK AT THIS AND DEDUCTIONS IN THE PROVISIONS
THAT COUNT TO THEM AND BRING US THAT FEEDBACK AS WELL. SO JIM,
I WANT TO STOP TO TAKE QUESTIONS FROM THE AUDIENCE.
BUT I WILL MAKE THE SAME REQUEST TO YOU AS WE DO TO
EVERYONE WE MEET, AND I'VE DONE MORE THAN 40 TOWN HALL MEETINGS
ON THIS BACK HOME, TRAVELED THE COUNTRY TO DO THE SAME, COAST
TO COAST TO LAY OUT THE GROWTH TAX FOREIGN PLAN AS WELL. TEST
DRIVE THIS. TEST DRIVE THIS PROPOSAL AND BRING US BACK YOUR
FEEDBACK. DON'T TAKE ONE PROVISION OUT OF THIS LIKE
INTEREST DEDUCTIBILITY AND DRIVE IT LIKE IT'S THAT OLD
CLUNKER OF A TAX CAR WE'RE IN TODAY. WHAT WE ARE PROPOSING IS
A NEW CAR. IT HAS DIFFERENT FEATURES. IT DRIVES MUCH
DIFFERENTLY. MOST ECONOMISTS BELIEVE DRIVES MUCH FASTER THAN
THE TAX CODE WE ARE IN TODAY. TEST DRIVE THE NEW PROPOSAL.
BRING US BACK THAT FEEDBACK, HELP US IMPROVE AT EVERY STEP.
THE TIME TABLE FOR US IS TO CONTINUE TO LISTEN TO THIS
FEEDBACK THROUGH THE END OF THE YEAR. OUR TAX TEAMS ARE WRITING
KEY PROVISIONS OF THIS AS WE SPEAK. WE ARE GETTING FEEDBACK
TO MAKE THIS BETTER AS WE WORK TOWARD INTRODUCING THIS EARLY
IN 2017. AND NOW BECAUSE WE HAVE A PRESIDENT WILLING TO
LEAD ON TAX REFORM IN MR. TRUMP. WHILE WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE THIS FITS, WE ARE READY TO DELIVER PRO GROWTH TAX
REFORM THAT LEAP FROGS AMERICA BACK INTO THE LEAD PACK AN
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU, CHAIRMAN BRADY. ASSOCIATION OF EQUIPMENT
MANUFACTURING. WANTED TO THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE TODAY AND
COMMEND YOUR STAFF FOR BEING INCREDIBLY EASY TO WORK WITH.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU. &gt;&gt; THANK YOU.
&gt;&gt; JUST LOOKING FOR YOUR THOUGHTS ON THE OPPORTUNITY TO
INCLUDE OR SOMEHOW MIRROR INFRASTRUCTURE INVESTMENT WITH
TAX REFORM. &gt;&gt; YEAH. SO THERE IS AN
INTEREST BY SOME TO USE THE REPATRIATED EARNINGS TO FUND
INFRASTRUCTURE IN SOME FORM OR FASHION. WE TOOK THE EARNINGS
FROM THE $2.5 TRILLION OF STRANDED U.S. PROFITS, BRING
BACK TO THE UNITED STATES. THOSE EARNINGS PILE BACK INTO
MORE COMPETITIVE TAX CODES. TO LOWER THE RATES, REDESIGN IT TO
COMPETE AND WIN ANYWHERE, ESPECIALLY HERE AT HOME. OTHERS
WOULD LIKE TO USE THAT FOR AN INFRASTRUCTURE RELATED
APPROACH. SO WE'LL LISTEN TO THOSE IDEAS. I THINK AT THE END
OF THE DAY, THE STRONG ECONOMY WE HAVE, THE MORE CERTAINTY AND
RESIGN THAT ACTUALLY GROWS THE ECONOMY IS AWFULLY IMPORTANT
FOR INVESTMENTS AND INFRASTRUCTURE OR ANYTHING
ELSE. WE KNOW WE'LL BE HAVING THESE DISCUSSIONS GOING
FORWARD. THANKS. &gt;&gt; LARRY HART WITH HART
STRATEGIES. THE WORK YOU'VE BEEN DOING ON THIS IS TERRIFIC
AND HEADED IN A DIRECTION THAT WE'VE WAITED TO GO FOR A LONG
TIME. I THINK THE QUESTION THAT OCCURS TO ME IN READING ABOUT
THIS IS WHEREAS IN THE HOUSE, THIS IS THE DIRECTION YOU'RE
GOING, THE SENATE DOESN'T SEEM TO BE ON THE SAME PLANET WHEN
WE TALK ABOUT THIS STUFF. THE BIG QUESTION COMES DOWN TO IS
TAX REFORM GOING TO BE DONE THROUGH THE RECONCILIATION
PROCESS? WHEN I THINK THAT YOU WOULD BE ABLE TO COME UP WITH A
BILL VERY MUCH ALONG THE LINES YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, ALONG
WITH WORKING WITH THE ADMINISTRATION ON DETAILS AND
THINGS LIKE THAT, OR WHETHER AT LEAST IN THE SENATE THEY'RE
GOING TO QUOTE/UNQUOTE HAVE A BIPARTISAN BILL. WHILE, YOU
KNOW, RECONCILIATION ONLY TAKES, YOU KNOW, IT'S ONLY GOOD
FOR TEN YEARS, AND IF THEY DO THAT, IF THEY WIND UP AGAIN AS
THEY DID A FEW YEARS AGO IN THE HOUSE PRENEGOTIATING WITH THE
DEMOCRATS ON A BILL, I CAN GUARANTEE YOU THERE WILL BE NO
ABOLISHMENT OF THE DEATH TAX. SOMETHING THAT WE HAVE, SOME OF YEARS AND SOME OTHER
PROVISIONS. IT WILL BE SOMETHING MORE LIKE A DEMOCRAT
BILL. HOW DO YOU SEE THAT RESOLVING?
&gt;&gt; WHILE A LOT OF PEOPLE NOW ARE BRAIN STORMING THE PROCESS
AND SEQUENCING AND TIMING, WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE IS FOCUSING
ON THE PRODUCT. DEVELOPING THE MOST PRO GROWTH, COMPETITIVE
TAX REFORM PROPOSAL WE CAN, RATHER THAN THE PROCESS OF
MOVING FORWARD. AND WHILE RECONCILIATION MAY BE THE ONLY
-- ULTIMATELY MAY BE THE ONLY OPTION, WE'RE GOING TO START
DIFFERENTLY. I'M INVITING OUR DEMOCRAT MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE
TO ENGAGE ON TAX REFORM. BRING US YOUR BEST IDEA ON HOW TO
GROW THE ECONOMY. BRING US YOUR BEST IDEA ON HOW TO MAKE THE
TAX CODE FAIR AND SIMPLE AGAIN FOR FAMILIES. THAT'S THE BEST
IDEA, YOUR BEST IDEAS AND HOW TO REDESIGN THE IRS IS
SOMETHING WE'LL BE FOCUSED ON CUSTOMER SERVICE. WE'LL LISTEN
TO THOSE IDEAS. HERE'S WHY I THINK WE ABSOLUTELY OUGHT TO,
BECAUSE OUR DEMOCRAT MEMBERS OF CONGRESS, I MEAN THEIR
COMMUNITIES ARE SUFFERING, TOO. THEIR COLLEGE KIDS AREN'T
FINDING THOSE JOBS. THEY'RE SEEING THE SAME COMPANIES WE
SEE CONSIDERING MOVING THEIR JOBS AND RESEARCH AND
INNOVATION HEADQUARTERS OVERSEAS. THEY CAN'T BE HAPPY
WITH THE STATUS QUO TODAY. SO WE'RE GOING TO OFFER A WIDE
OPEN OPPORTUNITY FOR OUR DEMOCRATS TO BRING THEIR BEST
IDEAS FORWARD AND ENGAGE ON TAX REFORM. HOW THAT PLAYS OUT AND
IF THEY'LL TAKE THAT OPPORTUNITY, I DON'T KNOW YET,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO OPEN THAT DOOR IN A MAJOR WAY. SO THAT'S
THE APPROACH I'M GOING TO TAKE. BY THE WAY, YOU START OUT WITH
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS PROPOSAL. DID I TELL YOU, WE INCORPORATED
THE IDEAS OF MORE THAN 50 LAW MAKERS IN THIS TAX REFORM
PROPOSAL. WE LOOKED AT THE THINKING OF THINK TANKS, PRO
GROWTH ORGANIZATIONS, PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES. THIS
IS NOT, THIS IS NOT, THIS IS NOT JUST A TAX PROPOSAL, IT IS
OURS FROM THE SENSE WE TOOK THE BEST IDEAS ON GROWTH SIMPLICITY
WE CAN IDENTIFY. WHICH IS WHY THIS IS IN THE HOUSE THE FIRST
CONSENSUS TAX REFORM BLUEPRINT IN MORE THAN 30 YEARS. IT'S WHY
IT MAKES IT MORE REAL GOING FORWARD, AND I THINK WE'VE GOT
A HEAD START ON MAKING SURE WE CAN DELIVER THIS IN 2017.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU, CHAIRMAN BRADY. IF YOU COULD TAKE ME A MINUTE
AND POINT OUT SIMILARITIES OR DIFFERENCES BETWEEN YOUR TAX
PLAN AND MR. TRUMP'S TAX PLAN AND THINGS WE SHOULD FOCUS ON,
THAT MIGHT BE HELPFUL. &gt;&gt; I THINK THE TAX PROPOSALS
ARE 80% THE SAME AND THE DIFFERENCES ARE MORE THAN
MANAGEABLE. WE CAN FIND COMMON GROUND HERE. WE GO ALL IN FOR
EXPENSING. IT'S INCREDIBLY PRO GROWTH ALONG MAIN STREET
AMERICA. THAT'S ONE CHANGE. WE ARE VERY AGGRESSIVE ON THE
INTERNATIONAL TAX REFORM. AND ON ELIMINATING THE INCENTIVES
TO LOCATE OVERSEAS, THE BORDER PROVISION ELIMINATES IT. IT
REVERSES THAT MAGNET BACK TOWARD THE U.S. WE THINK THAT'S
IMPORTANT TO GROWTH. WE'RE HOPEFUL THE TRUMP TEAM WILL
TAKE A LOOK AT PROPOSALS LIKE THAT. WE HAVE SIMILAR TAX
BRACKETS AS WELL. I DO THINK IN RECENT DAYS I'VE HEARD ONE
THOUGHT ABOUT THE WAGES AND TAXES OF THE TOP 1%, BUT HERE'S
MY THOUGHT. NO AMERICAN SHOULD BE STUCK WITH THE OBAMA TAX
RATES. THEY CERTAINLY HAVEN'T GROWN THE ECONOMY. THIS IS THE
WORST RECOVERY IN 50 YEARS. CERTAINLY HASN'T REDUCED INCOME
INEQUALITY, IT'S GROWN UNDER THIS PRESIDENT. AND THAT'S SORT
OF OLD TIME THINKING. HIGH TAX RATES, HUNDREDS OF PROVISIONS
AND TRY TO PHASE THEM OUT OR LIMIT THEM. OUR PROPOSAL IS
MUCH DIFFERENT. ON THE POST CARD, WE'RE PROPOSING EVERYONE
KNOW EXACTLY WHAT EACH OTHER'S DEDUCTIONS ARE. WE LOWER THOSE
RATES SO THE HELP YOU GET FROM HOME AND CHARITY, KIDS IN
COLLEGE, EVERYONE KNOWS WHAT THEY ARE BECAUSE THEY'RE
EXACTLY THE SAME FOR EVERYBODY. SO WE'RE THINKING DIFFERENTLY
ABOUT HOW YOU ADDRESS TAX REFORM AT EVERY TAX BRACKET
INCLUDING THOSE AT THE 1%. &gt;&gt; TIM BROWN. I WANT TO SAY I
APPRECIATE YOUR COMMENTS. I'M REPRESENTING MYSELF. I'M A
CITIZEN AND TAXPAYER AND A VOTER. IT SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
YOU ALLOWED TO ONE POINT I WOULD LIKE YOU TO AMPLIFY ON.
I'M AWARE THE HIGHEST TAX RATES ARE ON PEOPLE AT A WELFARE
STANDARD IF YOU LOOK AT WELFARE EFFECTS AS A TAX. CAN YOU SAY
MORE ABOUT HOW THE TAX PROGRAM WILL HELP THE POOREST OF THE
POOR HAVE AN INCENTIVE TO WORK?
&gt;&gt; SURE. SO THERE IS NO QUICKER PATH OUT OF POVERTY THAN A JOB,
EVEN FASTER, A GOOD-PAYING JOB. IT'S ONE OF THE MISSING
INGREDIENTS IN THE OBAMA RECOVERY IN A MAJOR WAY. NOT
JUST THOSE ON WELFARE, YOUNG PEOPLE, MIDDLE CLASS, ALL BUT
THE ELDERLY, FRANKLY, THEIR PERCENTAGE HAS SHRUNK WITHIN
THE WORK FORCE. THIS AIMS TO REVERSE THAT, CREATE MORE GOOD
PAYING JOBS, WHICH IS REALLY KEY FOR THOSE TRYING TO WORK
THEIR WAY UP THE ECONOMIC LADDER. SO WE THINK THAT'S THE
ULTIMATE ANSWER. COUPLED WITH REGULATORY REFORM SO BUSINESSES
ARE CREATING MORE OF THOSE MAINSTREAM JOBS. A COUPLE IN MY
VIEW WITH SEARCHING FOR MORE CUSTOMERS FOR AMERICAN PRODUCTS
AROUND THE WORLD, BETTER, ENFORCIBLE, PRODUCTIVE TRADE
AGREEMENTS ARE IMPORTANT AS WELL FOR TRADING JOBS HERE IN
THE UNITED STATES. AND IN THE BETTER WAY AGENDA, WE PROPOSE A
NEW WAY OF LOOKING AT WELFARE. TODAY, THINK ABOUT THIS, THERE
ARE MORE PEOPLE ON WELFARE THAN ARE WORKING FULL TIME. TAKE
EVERY MAN, WOMAN AND CHILD IN 24 STATES TOTAL, THAT'S THE
NUMBER OF AMERICANS IN POVERTY TODAY. IT'S STUCK THERE. IT'S
NOT GETTING BETTER AND IT WON'T IMPROVE UNLESS WE RETHINK THE
WAY WE ADDRESS WELFARE. SO IN OUR BETTER WAY AGENDA, WE LAY
OUT FOUR KEY PRINCIPLES THAT ARE GAME-CHANGING BUT WE KNOW
WORK AT THE LOCAL LEVEL STARTING WITH REQUIRING AND
EXPECTING WORK FOR THESE WELFARE BENEFITS BECAUSE THAT'S
THE KEY ACCESS POINT OUT OF THERE. SO IT WON'T BE ACHIEVED,
MY ANSWER IS IT WON'T BE ACHIEVED MERELY THROUGH A FAIR
AND SIMPLER AND MORE PRO-GROWTH TAX CODE BUT IT CAN BE IF WE
THINK DIFFERENTLY ABOUT HOW WE</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5841548dca5055000602a956_0</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480678665830.1480676452094.fc230aa2-1de7-4988-b2fa-b6f7e7363854.segment0.thumb.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 11:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <segment:duration>1125.964</segment:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Journal</title>
      <link>http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480676452094.fc230aa2-1de7-4988-b2fa-b6f7e7363854.mp4#t=1125.96,1194.97</link>
      <description>ADDRESS THE ISSUE. &gt;
&gt;&gt;&gt; CHAIRMAN BRADY, THANKS FOR BEING HERE TODAY. I WANT YOU TO
KNOW HOW MUCH WE APPRECIATE THE ATTENTION AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENT
WE NEED FOR RATE REDUCTION ACROSS THE BOARD THAT. WILL BE
HUGELY IMPORTANT TO BRINGING BACK THE JOBS AND INVESTMENT WE
NEED HERE AT HOME. I WAS WONDERING IF YOU COULD TALK A
LITTLE BIT BEGIN HOW MUCH WORK YOU WILL HAVE IN CONGRESS
COMING IN EARLY NEXT YEAR ABOUT THE TIMELINE AND SEQUENCING
WILL BE FOR TAX REFORM. &gt;&gt; IT'S DIFFICULT TO KNOW NOW.
WE WANT TO KNOW WHERE -- THE TRUMP TEAM HAS JUST BEEN A FEW
WEEKS. THEY DESERVE THE CHANCE TO FILL THE TEAM OUT, THINK
ABOUT THE FIRST 100 DAYS TO GET THEIR FEET ON THE GROUND THERE.
SO WE'LL CONTINUE -- WE'RE ENGAGED WITH THEM NOW. WE'LL
CONTINUE TO STAY ENGAGED WITH THEM AS WE WORK OUT SORT OF
SOME FINDING COMMON GROUNDS ON ISSUES LIKE TAX REFORM AND
LEARN MORE ABOUT THEIR TIMING. WHAT I'M HERE TO SAY IS THAT
WE'RE NOT FOCUSED ON THE PROCESS IN THIS TIMING, WE ARE
FOCUSED WHENEVER THAT IS SET, WE ARE GOING TO BE READY TO
DELIVER PRO GROWTH TAX REFORM. SO THAT'S EXACTLY WHERE WE'RE
AT RIGHT NOW. &gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5841548dca5055000602a956_1</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480678759178.1480676452094.fc230aa2-1de7-4988-b2fa-b6f7e7363854.segment1.thumb.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 11:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <segment:duration>69.003</segment:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Journal</title>
      <link>http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480676452094.fc230aa2-1de7-4988-b2fa-b6f7e7363854.mp4#t=1194.97,1799.10</link>
      <description>&gt;&gt;&gt; I GET YOUR POINT ABOUT THE
EXPENSING AND THE INTEREST FACTOR. IF YOU TAKE THAT
EXTENSION OVER TO HOME MORTGAGES AND ALLOWED TO WRITE
OFF THE HOME MORTGAGE INTEREST, WOULD YOU NOT BE ALLOWED TO
WRITE OFF COMMERCIAL PROPERTY INTEREST ON A COMMERCIAL
LOAN? &gt;&gt; WE ARE PROPOSING NOT TO DO
THAT. WE ARE ACTUALLY SORT OF PUTTING THE HOME MORTGAGE
DEDUCTION IN A SEPARATE CATEGORY. BECAUSE AS WE LOOK AT
THE POST CARD, I THINK WHILE SOME WOULD LIKE TO HAVE FIGHTS
OVER INDIVIDUAL PROVISIONS IN THE TAX CODE, THE DEBATE THAT
WE'RE LOOKING FOR IN AMERICA IS WHETHER AMERICANS WANT
SOMETHING THIS FAIR AND THIS SIMPLE AND THIS UNDERSTANDABLE
AND ARE WILLING TO MAKE THE TRADE-OFFS TO GET THERE, OR WE
WANT TO STICK WITH THE STATUS QUO? OVERWHELMINGLY COMPLEX TAX
CODE, WHO KNOW ONE KNOWS HOW PROVISIONS ARE APPLIED. WE ARE
PROPOSING A GAME-CHANGING APPROACH HOW WE ADDRESS THAT.
FOR MANY FAMILIES A HOME MORTGAGE DEDUCTION IS SOMETHING
THEY COUNT ON. SO THAT IS WHY IT WILL STAY -- WE'RE PROPOSING
TO YOU TO KEEP IT WITHIN THE TAX CODE. FOR REAL ESTATE OR
ANY INDUSTRY, ECONOMY GROWING AT BETTER THAN 3% OR CLOSER TO
4% IS DRAMATICALLY BETTER THAN 1.5% AND 1.75% WE'VE GOT TODAY.
LOWER TAX RATES ALLOWS THEM TO CONTINUE TO KEEP MONEY INVESTED
LOCALLY. THE ABILITY TO NOT JUST GROW THE ECONOMY BUT
PRODUCTIVITY AND WAGES FOR WORKERS IS AWFULLY IMPORTANT
WHETHER YOU'RE IN COMMERCIAL REAL ESTATE OR THAT DONUT SHOP
OWNER. I KEEP COMING BACK TO THAT. SO WE'RE HOPING AND
ASKING THAT EVERY INDUSTRY TAKE A LOOK AT THE ENTIRE BLUEPRINT,
INCLUDING THE PROVISIONS THAT CHANGE THAT ECONOMY IN A VERY
POSITIVE WAY AND LOOK AT THE IMPACT IT HAS ON THE INDUSTRY.
WE WANT THAT FEEDBACK. WE'RE LOOKING TO IMPROVE AND MAKE
THIS BETTER AT EVERY STEP SO ENGAGE WITH US. I'LL FINISH
WITH THIS. WE CAN DO THIS. IT'S BEEN 30 YEARS. I THINK THE
BIGGEST CHALLENGE THE TAX REFORM IS MOST AMERICANS HAVE
GIVEN UP HOPE IT WILL EVER HAPPEN. WHAT'S OCCURRING TODAY
IS WHAT IS OCCURRING -- OCCURRED FOR PRESIDENT REAGAN.
THREE MAJOR CHANGES HAPPENING IN AMERICA TODAY. ONE AS WITH
PRESIDENT REAGAN'S REFORM, THE AMERICAN PUBLIC WAS SICK OF THE
TAX CODE. TOO COMPLEX, TOO COSTLY, LOOPHOLES FOR
EVERYBODY, HEADACHES FOR THEM, THEY HAD ENOUGH. THAT'S WHERE
WE'RE AT TODAY. SECONDLY, THEY WERE BOLD IDEAS ON TAX REFORM
BY LAW MAKERS. AND OTHERS. THEN IT WAS THE JACK KEMPE AND BILL
BRADLEY. TODAY WE'VE GOT FAIR TAX, FLAT TAX, ABC TAX, WE HAVE
PROVISIONS, SMART IDEAS ON TAX REFORM. WE HAVE THE SAME
DYNAMIC. THIRD DYNAMIC THEN WE HAD A PRESIDENT WILLING TO LEAD
ON TAX REFORM. TODAY WE HAVE A NEW PRESIDENT COMING INTO
OFFICE WILLING TO LEAD ON TAX REFORM. THOSE DYNAMICS THAT
EXISTED FOR THE '86 REFORMS HAVE REOCCURRED AGAIN IN A
MAJOR WAY. THIS IS A UNIQUE OPPORTUNITY FOR US TO DO WHAT
MOST AMERICANS HAVE GIVEN OF HOPE EVER WILL HAPPEN. IT'S A
DRAMATIC OPPORTUNITY TO LEAP FROG AMERICA BACK IN THE MOST
COMPETITIVE PLACE ON THE PLANET TO CREATE THAT NEW JOB. WE ARE
DETERMINED TO DELIVER ON THAT. THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR HAVING
ME HERE TODAY. &gt;&gt; IF OUR PANEL WOULD LIKE TO
JOIN US HERE ON THE STAGE, WE'LL CONTINUE THIS DISCUSSION.
AND I WILL TURN THE PROGRAM OVER TO MY COLLEAGUE DAVID
BURTON. WHEN WE ARE TALKING CONGRESS, I ALWAYS WANT TO CALL
YOU DAN BURTON FOR SOME REASON. EXCUSE ME IF I SLIP INTO THAT.
DAVID BURTON IS OUR SENIOR FELLOW IN THOMAS A. ROWE
INSTITUTE FOR ECONOMIC POLICY STUDIES AND HE WILL LEAD THE
REST OF THIS DISCUSSION. DAVID?
&gt;&gt; IT'S MY PLEASURE TO INTRODUCE THREE VERY HIGH
QUALITY PANELISTS. I'VE ASKED THEM TO EACH SPEAK FOR ABOUT 10
MINUTES AND WE'LL HAVE A QUESTION AND ANSWER SESSION AND
A DISCUSSION. WE'RE GOING TO GO FIRST WITH JASON THEN STEVE
BENTON THEN DAN MITCHELL. JASON IS A SENIOR RESEARCH FELLOW AT
THE MERCADA CENTER GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY AND TEACHES
ECONOMICS AT THE JOHNS HOPKINS AND VIRGINIA TECH. HE IS A
FORMER ACTING ASSISTANT COMMISSIONER AT SOCIAL SECURITY
ADMINISTRATION AND CHIEF ECONOMIST THERE. SERVED AS
JOINT ECONOMIC COMMITTEE AS AN ECONOMIST AND IS A VERY FINE
PUBLIC FINANCE ECONOMIST WORKING BOTH IN TAX POLICY AND
ENTITLEMENTS. STEPHEN IS A SENIOR FELLOW AT THE TAX
FOUNDATION. HE WENT TO THE UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO AS DID I,
BUT STEVE UNLIKE ME ACTUALLY LEARNED SOMETHING WHILE HE WAS
THERE. HE SERVED IN THE REAGAN TREASURY, WAS AT THE INSTITUTE
OF RESEARCH ON ECONOMICS OF TAXATION FOR MANY YEARS, AND
AFTER NORM DIED SERVED AS ITS PRESIDENT. HE IS AN EXTREMELY
FINE TAX ECONOMIST AND HE AND HIS COLLEAGUES AND FOUNDATION
PUT TOGETHER COMPUTABLE TAX POLICY MODEL THERE THAT IS
SECOND TO NONE, ACTUALLY PROBABLY MORE BETTER, IT'S THE
VERY BEST IN THE UNITED STATES. DAN MITCHELL IS A SENIOR FELLOW
AT THE CATO INSTITUTE. HE IS, WHEN ADVOCATING FOR TAX
REFORMS, HE DOESN'T KNOW THE MEANING OF THE WORD FEAR, BUT
IN SOME RESPECTS, THAT SHOULD BE UNSURPRISING BECAUSE THERE
ARE LOTS OF WORDS DAN DOESN'T KNOW THE MEANING OF.
&gt;&gt; YOU CAN SEE WHY I COME HERE ALL THE TIME. I GET NOTHING BUT
PRAISE. &gt;&gt; DAN WORKED FOR SENATOR
PACKWOOD DURING THE '86 TAX REFORM ACT THE LAST TIME WE GOT
SUBSTANTIAL POSITIVE TAX REFORM DONE. HE ONCE UPON A TIME
WORKED HERE AT THE HERITAGE FOUNDATION. IT'S MY
UNDERSTANDING BEFORE I WAS HERE. IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING DAN
HERE PEOPLE HAVE SINCE REPRESSED THEIR MEMORIES OF HIS
STAY HERE. WE HAVE A VERY FINE PANEL. BEFORE WE GET TO THAT, I
WANT TO TAKE TWO OR THREE MINUTES AND DISCUSS TAX REFORM,
THE OPPORTUNITY WE HAVE TO GET SOMETHING VERY POSITIVE DONE
FOR THE AMERICAN PEOPLE AND A FEW THOUGHTS ABOUT WHAT THAT
MIGHT BE. IT'S WELL ESTABLISHED THAT IF YOU'RE TRYING TO CREATE
ECONOMIC GROWTH AND OPPORTUNITY YOU WANT TO REDUCE MARGINAL TAX
RATES AND MOVE TOWARDS A CONSUMPTION TAX RATE. IN MICRO
ECONOMIC TERMS THAT MEANS THAT YOU SHOULD REDUCE MARGINAL TAX
RATES AND MOVE TO A TAX BASE SO YOU REDUCE WHAT ECONOMISTS WHO
CALL DEAD WEIGHT LOSS OR EXCESS BURDEN. THAT IS THE LOST
ECONOMIC OUTPUT BECAUSE OF THE EFFECTS OF TAX POLICY. THIS IS
SOMETHING ANYBODY WHO'S HAD THE JOYS OF INTRODUCTORY PRICE
THEORY CAN DO. THE MOST IMPORTANT THING TO REMEMBER
ABOUT THAT IS THAT THE BENEFIT OF REDUCING MARGINAL TAX RATES
INCREASES WITH THE SQUARE OF THE TAX RATE REDUCTION AND THE
CONVERSE IS ALSO TRUE, THE ECONOMIC LOSSES INCREASE WITH
THE SQUARE OF THE INCREASE IN THE TAX RATE. OPTIMAL TAX
THEORY IS THE SAME RESULT. IF YOU LOOK AT OPTIMAL TAX
LITERATURE GOING BACK AND ITS ANALYSIS OF INTERTEMPORAL
CHOICES, YOU WANT TO HAVE A CONSUMPTION BASE WHICH MOST
MAJOR TAX REFORM PROPOSALS LEAD THE PUBLIC FINANCE LITERATURE
LEADS TO THE SAME CONCLUSION. IF YOU WANT TO HAVE A TAX SYSTEM
THAT'S NEUTRAL WITH RESPECT TO ALL THE FACTORS OF PRODUCTION,
YOU MOVED TO A CONSUMPTION-BASED, INCOME TAX
DOUBLE, TROUBLE AND SOMETIMES QUADRUPLE TAXES.
CAPITAL AND THEREFORE LEADS TO AN INEFFICIENT, UNPRODUCTIVE TAX
SYSTEM. WE WANT TO ELIMINATE TAX
PREFERENCES. WHY?
THERE'S TWO BASIC TAX PREFERENCES.
TAX PREFERENCES FOR VARIOUS PRODUCERS DISTORT THE ECONOMY
AND LEAD TO AN INEFFICIENT PRODUCTION PROCESS AND
INEFFICIENT NONECONOMIC CHOICES BY THE PRODUCERS.
WHAT AN ECONOMIST WOULD SAY IS IT SHRINKS THE PRODUCTION
POSSIBILITIES FRONTIER. ON THE CONSUMER SIDE, WHEN YOU
ALTER PEOPLE'S CHOICES FOR COMPARABLE REASONS, YOU GET AN
INEFFICIENT ABILITY OF THE ECONOMY TO SATISFY CONSUMER
WANTS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5841548dca5055000602a956_2</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480678859282.1480676452094.fc230aa2-1de7-4988-b2fa-b6f7e7363854.segment2.thumb.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 11:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <segment:duration>604.136</segment:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
