<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:segment="https://github.com/Viral-MediaLab/superglue-rss" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>bloomberg tv</title>
    <link>http://www.bloomberg.com/live</link>
    <description>bloomberg tv</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 20:15:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What'd You Miss?</title>
      <link>http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1482174205481.9c79d857-8ba7-45df-b3be-aba9c306a9d5.mp4#t=0.00,936.54</link>
      <description>SCARLET: THANK YOU.
WE ARE READING -- WE ARE WAITING FOR FED CHAIR JANET YELLEN TO
TAKE THE STAND AT THE COMMENCEMENT CEREMONY.
SHE RELEASED THE TEXT OF HER REMARKS, THERE'S NO MENTION ON
POLICY REAGANOMICS OUTLOOK. THIS IS BLOOMBERG.
♪ SCARLET: THIS IS "BLOOMBERG
MARKETS," I'M SCARLET FU. WE HAD TO ABIGAIL DOOLITTLE, WHO
HAS THREE CHARTS OF THE DAY. ABIGAIL: WE START WITH A
LONG-TERM CHART OF THE DOLLAR-YEN, G #BTB 5395.
WE SEE THE MASSIVE DOWNTREND GOING BACK TO 1970.
EVEN THOUGH A BIG STORY IN RECENT YEARS IS THE WEAKNESS IN
THE END AND THE STRENGTHEN THE DOLLAR -- IN THE YEN AND THE
STRENGTH IN THE DOLLAR ON THE LONG-TERM DOWNTURN REMAINS IN
EFFECT. THE SECOND CHART, ONE IS AROUND
THE 10 YEAR YIELD, NOT SURPRISINGLY, THE DOLLAR-YEN IS
HIGHLY COORDINATED TO THE 10 YEAR YIELD.
AND THEN WHITE, YOU SEE THE 10 YEAR YIELD AN ORANGE, THE
DOLLAR-YEN. IF THAT DOES REMAIN IN EFFECT,
IT MAY SUGGEST THE MASSIVE MOVE WE'VE SEEN IN YIELD RECENTLY,
100 BASIS POINTS, THE BIGGEST MOVE ON THE QUARTER SO FAR COULD
RETREAT TO SOME DEGREE. OF COURSE, THAT WOULD SUGGEST WE
COULD SEE VOLATILITY ACROSS THE OTHER ASSET CLASSES.
GOES INTO COMMODITIES ALONG WITH EQUITIES.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT VOLATILITY BECAUSE YOU HAD FOR STOCKS AT G
#BTB 4350. IN WHITE, THE S&amp;P 500, AND WHITE
UNDER THE VIX. IT SUGGESTS TRUMPS -- INVESTORS
ARE COMPLACENT. THE S&amp;P 500 SUGGESTS WE'VE SEEN
THE TO RECONVERT. WE SEE A SPIKE UP ON THE VIX,
THE QUOTE UNQUOTE FEAR INDEX AND A MOVE DOWN AND STOCKS.
ALL OF THIS MAY SUGGEST A LITTLE BIT OF A BREATHER IS AHEAD FOR
STOCKS AND SOME REVERSALS ON SOME OF THESE BIG MOVES OUT OF
THE ELECTION. SCARLET: I LOVE ANY CHART WITH
THE VIX. LET'S GET INTO THE BLOOMBERG
BUSINESS FLASH AND A LOOK AT THE BUSINESS STORIES IN THE NEWS.
DEUTSCHE BANK COULD PAY FAR LESS THAN THE $14 BILLION FIND THAT
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE WANTS TO SETTLE A MORTGAGE SECURITY
PROBE. AS ACCORDING TO A REPORT FROM
REUTERS WHO CITES A PERSON FAMILIAR WITH THE MATTER.
IS ALSO A GOOD CHANCE THE MATTER WILL BE RESOLVED THIS WEEK,
PROBABLY AS EARLY AS WEDNESDAY. FRENCH DRIVERS ARE ASKING UBER
FOR A RAISE, RAILS. LABOR UNIONS AND ADVISERS OF
FRANCE'S TRANSPORT MINISTERS, DRIVERS ARE THREATENING TO
STRIKE AGAIN IF THEY DON'T HIKE PRICES OR LOWER BECAUSE OF THE
COMPANY TAKES FROM EACH FAIR. MOSAIC IS BUYING THE FERTILIZER
UNIT FOR $2.5 BILLION IN CASH AND STOCKS TO BECOME THE BIGGEST
FOR LASER PRODUCER IN BRAZIL. HALF OF THE PRICE WILL BE PAID
IN CASH AND THE OTHER HALF IN NEW EQUITY, GIVING THEM AN 11%
STAKE IN MOSAIC AND TWO SEATS ON THE BOARD.
THE TRANSACTION IS EXPECTED TO CLOSE LATE NEXT YEAR.
THAT IS YOUR BUSINESS FLASH UPDATE.
REGULARS ARE SOUNDING THE ALARM ABOUT TAINTED SEAFOOD AND
AMERICAN SUPERMARKETS. CRACKING DOWN ON THE PROBLEM
ISN'T QUITE SO EASY. CAROL MASSAR AND OLIVER RENICK
SPOKE TO MEGAN MURPHY ABOUT THE STORY.
MEGAN: THE FIRST THING THAT POPPED OUT IS IN THE CONTEXT
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT, WITH CHINA AND THE GLOBAL ECONOMY.
THE STORY REALLY TRACES HOW SOMETHING YOU DON'T THINK THAT
MUCH ABOUT, WHICH IS WHEN YOU ARE EATING SEAFOOD OR SHRIMP OR
ANYTHING, JUST THE CHAIN IT GOES THROUGH AND WHERE THE PROMINENCE
OF THAT IS AND HOW THINGS YOU DON'T KNOW CAN GET INTO THE FOOD
SUPPLY. IT PRESENTS A TALE OF AN ECONOMY
THAT IS RAPIDLY TRANSFORMING, IN A REVELATORY ENVIRONMENT THAT
FRANKLY LEAVES A LOT TO BE DESIRED IN TERMS OF WHAT
ACTUALLY GOES INTO OUR FOOD. WE HAVE U.S. REGULARS PUTTING
TARIFFS ON CHINESE SHRIMP, AND THEY FOUND WAYS TO GET AROUND
IT. THEY CONTINUE TO.
MEGAN: A REALLY TRACES THROUGH THAT.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU WOULD CALL THE LOOPHOLES, THE WAYS THEY
EVADED REGULAR TORY SCRUTINY, NOT FROM A LACK OF INTENTIONAL
MISFEASANCE, BUT THE VERY FACT OF THEM WANTING TO GET STUFF
DONE, AND HOW THEY WANT TO -- ONE SUPPLIERS MAJOR THEY ARE
FISHING AND HAVE A ROBUST ENVIRONMENT AND WHAT HAPPENS
THERE. THE CONTRARY EFFECT OF THAT IS
IT SEEPS IN AND YOU DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHAT IS GOING ON AND
WHAT IS HAPPENING WHERE THESE THINGS ARE LIVING AND BREATHING.
AND THE EFFECT OF HAVING A SUPERBUG POSSIBILITY COMING IN
TO THIS KIND OF STREAM. THAT'S THE CONCERN.
IT ALMOST READS LIKE A MOVIE, WHEN YOU READ THE STORY.
IT'S A TALE WE'VE SEEN PLAY OUT ON THE BIG SCREEN BEFORE.
IT READS VERY MUCH LIKE THAT, SOMETHING THAT SEEMS RELATIVELY
INNOCUOUS, BUT THROUGH LACK OF REGULATORY OVERSIGHT, DESIRE FOR
A HIGHER-MARGIN AND HIGHER PROFIT, AND FRIENDLY,
CARELESSNESS IN TERMS OF A PART OF THE WORLD HAS VERY DIFFERENT
STANDARDS THAN WE WOULD EXPECT IN THE U.S. AND OTHER PARTS OF
THE WORLD. OLIVER: LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
SCIENCE OF WHAT'S HAPPENING. BASICALLY, THERE'S HIS ECOSYSTEM
THAT EXISTS THAT IS GETTING POLLUTED IN SOME SENSE.
NOT IN THE WAY WE TYPICALLY THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S ABOUT WORKING ITS WAY THROUGH THE SYSTEM AND BUILDING
UP IN THE FOOD THAT WE EAT. MEGAN: IT'S A STORY OF SOMETHING
THAT IS DESIGNED TO BE GOOD AND IMPROVE PARTS OF THE ECOSYSTEM,
CAN MANIFEST ITSELF IN WAYS THAT WE DON'T CURRENTLY HAVE A
STRUCTURE IN PLACE TO DEAL WITH IT.
IT WEAVES ITS WAY THROUGH IN A WAY THE SYSTEM IS NOT DESIGNED
TO CATCH. WE DISCOVERED HOW THIS IS
FILTERING IN TO THE U.S. AND INTO OTHER COUNTRIES IN A WAY
THAT PEOPLE WOULD NEVER THINK COULD HAPPEN.
PARTICULARLY ONE OF THE THINGS I REALLY LOVE ABOUT THE STORY, THE
IMAGERY OF THE STORY OF PIGS NEXT TO DISCARDED MEDICINES AND
DISCARDED AS ABOUT X. -- ANTIBIOTICS.
PEOPLE SHOVELING FROM -- EXCREMENT FROM ANIMALS INTO THE
SAME PART OF THAT ECOSYSTEM WHERE SHRIMP AND OTHER WILDLIFE
IS LIVING AND BREATHING. OLIVER: I WAS THINKING OF A
DIAGRAM IN MIDDLE SCHOOL, ARROWS GOING FROM HERE TO THERE.
IT'S NOT PLEASANT. MEGAN: AQUACULTURE FOR THOUSANDS
OF YEARS WORKED WELL IN CHINA. WHEN YOU INTRODUCE ANTIBIOTICS
INTO THE EQUATION. WE ARE MORE SENSITIVE ABOUT THE
INCREASED USE OF ANTIBIOTICS AND HOW IT IS CREATING SUPERBUGS AND
ILLNESSES AND PROBLEMS WITH PEOPLE.
MEGAN: WHEN WE GO BACK TO GLOBALIZATION, WE'VE SEEN THIS
PLAY OUT IN WESTERN WORLD AND THE EASTERN WORLD AS WELL PEOPLE
MOVE AT DIFFERENT SPEAKS. ECONOMIES ARE MOVING A VERY
DIFFERENT SPEED AND THEY WILL TAKE THEIR ADVANTAGE WHERE THEY
CAN, IN TERMS OF EXPLOITING REVELATORY ARBITRAGE.
I THINK THIS STORY IS ABOUT THAT, WHERE ANTIBIOTICS HAVE
BEEN INTRODUCED AS BENEFICIAL TO THAT PART OF THE ECONOMY.
IT'S JUST THAT ON THE END PRODUCT OF THE ECONOMY, ON THE
MORE DEVELOPED WORLD SIDE, THAT'S WHERE PROBLEMS ARE
EMERGING. THAT'S GOING TO BE ATTENTION
THAT PLAYS OUT THROUGHOUT SOCIETY SO MUCH MORE, AND IT'S
REALLY ACCELERATING. I THINK OVER THE NEXT DECADE,
IT'S GOING TO BE ONE OF THE BIGGEST THINGS OF WHERE THIS
REGULATORY ARBITRAGE IS -- IS THERE A NEED FOR OVERSIGHT OF
THE SECTOR, WHERE YOU HAVE UNPREDICTABLE EFFECTS OF WHAT IS
ACTUALLY DESIGNED TO BE A GOOD THING FOR AN ECONOMY.
SCARLET: YOU CAN READ THE LATEST STORY IN THE LATEST BLOOMBERG
BUSINESSWEEK AND HEAR MORE FROM THE MAGAZINE REPORTERS EVERY
SATURDAY AND SUNDAY ON BLOOMBERG TELEVISION.
COMING UP, WARREN BUFFETT MAKES HIS BIGGEST FOR JUST YET.
THE DETAILS ON ALMOST $5 BILLION TRANSACTION.
FROM NEW YORK, THIS IS BLOOMBERG.
♪ SCARLET: THIS IS "BLOOMBERG
MARKETS," I'M SCARLET FU. THE CANADIAN INVESTOR KNOWN AS
THE WARREN BUFFETT OF THE NORTH MADE A HUGE BET ON WHAT HE CALLS
U.S. ECONOMIC STRAINS UNDER A TRUCK -- FROM -- TRUMP
PRESIDENCY. TELL US MORE ABOUT THE WARREN
BUFFETT OF THE NORTH. &gt;&gt; PREM WATSA
IS THE CEO OF FAIRFAX FINANCIAL. HE'S A RECLUSIVE, QUIET FIGURE.
A SIMILAR SILENT INVESTMENT WARREN BUFFETT.
IT'SALSO $5 BILLION DEAL, THE BIGGEST FAIRFAX FINANCIAL HAS
MADE IN 31 YEARS. PREM WATSA IS CALLING IT A
TRANSFORMATIVE DEAL. THEY ARE BUYING A SWISS COMPANY
WITH HUGE EXPOSURE TO THE UNITED STATES, ALLIED WORLD INSURANCE.
THEY LEAVE THE CURRENT CEO VERY MUCH IN CHARGE OF THAT SIDE OF
THE BUSINESS. BUT IT IS A BET HE SAYS, IN HIS
WORDS, ON THE NEW ERA THAT IS BEING SWEPT FOURTH BECAUSE OF
THE TRUMP ELECTION. AS OF THE ELECTION, THE
REPUBLICAN CONTROL AND SENATE AND CONGRESS, STRONG POTENTIAL
TO MAKE THE BUSINESS CLIMATE FOR GROWTH, MAKING THE U.S. GREAT
AGAIN. RELATIVE TO THE REST OF THE
WORLD. THAT IS HIS REASONING FOR THIS
DEAL THAT'S BEEN ANNOUNCED TODAY IN AN ARTICLE.
THE ALLIED DEAL LOOKS LIKE IT WILL GIVE FAIRFAX AN INVESTMENT
PORTFOLIO BOOSTED UP TO $39 MILLION FROM ABOUT $30 BILLION.
SO THEY TAKE INSURANCE PREMIUMS AND USE THOSE TO INVEST IN
DIFFERENT INDUSTRIES. SCARLET: WHEN YOU LOOK AT PREM
WATSA, HE'S A BIG BELIEVER IN CANADIAN TECHNOLOGY, MAINLY
BLACKBERRY.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58582f07837ad70006f116ef_0</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1482176867623.1482174205481.9c79d857-8ba7-45df-b3be-aba9c306a9d5.segment0.thumb.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 19:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <segment:duration>936.536</segment:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What'd You Miss?</title>
      <link>http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1482174205481.9c79d857-8ba7-45df-b3be-aba9c306a9d5.mp4#t=936.54,1798.03</link>
      <description>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BLACKBERRY, FAIRFAX IS ONEF
THE LARGEST STAKEHOLDERS IN BLACKBERRY.
A HUGE BET ON A COMPANY THAT, AS MOST PEOPLE KNOW, HAS JUST
DROPPED ITS WAY FURTHER AND FURTHER DOWN.
BLACKBERRY OUT WITH ANNOUNCEMENTS TODAY THAT IT IS
WORKING WITH CANADA AND THE GOVERNMENT TO OPEN A RESEARCH
CENTER FOR SELF DRIVING CARS. THE QNX SIDE OF THE BUSINESS IS
A PART OF THE BUSINESS FOR BLACKBERRY.
THEY ALWAYS POINTED TO, IT'S BEEN BUILDING SOFTWARE TO RUN IN
CAR ENTERTAINMENT FOR A LONG TIME.
THIS IS A NEW SHIFT INTO THE SELF DRIVING CAR SIDE OF THINGS.
WHO KNOWS, THEY DO THAT WILL PAY OFF FOR BLACKBERRY.
SCARLET: YOU BEEN FOLLOWING NEWS THAT LARGEST BUYOUT FIRM HAS
BEEN PAYING UP FOR A U.K. HOLIDAY PARK ANTHONY.
TELL US MORE ABOUT THIS DEAL. &gt;&gt; IT'S INTERESTING.
THESE ARE CARAVAN HOLIDAY PARKS OR RV RESORTS IN THE U.K..
ON NEXT -- ONEX HAS ANNOUNCED THEY WOULD LIKE TO ACQUIRE
PARKING RESORTS FOR 1.59 BILLION DOLLARS, EXPECTED TO CLOSE SOME
TIME IN THE FIRST QUARTER OF NEXT YEAR.
THE COMPANY OPERATES 73 CARAVAN HOLIDAY PARKS ACROSS THE U.K., A
BIG BET ON THE MIDDLE CLASS. SCARLET: WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON
THAT ONE. PAMELA RITCHIE JOINING US FROM
TORONTO. I WANT TO GO BACK TO HEADLINES
WE BROKE EARLIER IN THE HOUR ABOUT ITALY WEIGHING AN INCREASE
IN PUBLIC DEBT FOR BANKS. THEN CURTIS FOLLOWED UP AND CAME
UP WITH THIS CHART ON THE BLOOMBERG.
TAKE A LOOK, IT SHOWS BASICALLY THE OUTSTANDING DEBT THAT IS
THERE FOR ITALY. IN 2015, A PRETTY SMALL NUMBER,
BUT YOU CAN SEE THAT THINGS A SKYROCKET IN 2017.
THE BLUE SIDE OF THE BAR IS THE BOND PRINCIPAL AND THE YELLOW
PORTION IS THE INTEREST. AND THEN IT COMES BACK DOWN
AGAIN. ITALY'S CABINET MEETING IN ROME
THIS EVENING TO ASK AUTHORIZATION FROM PARLIAMENT TO
INCREASE PUBLIC DEBT. THE GOVERNMENT IS PREPARING
POTENTIAL INVESTMENT IN THE COMPANY'S BANK -- IN THE
COUNTRY'S BANK. THIS IS AS ITALY TRIES TO
PREPARE A PLAN TO INJECT UP TO 15 BILLION EUROS INTO ITALIAN
BANKS IS MONTE PASCHI IS FUNDRAISING DOES NOT COME TO
PASS. THIS PLAN WILL BE IMPLEMENTED
ONLY IF NEEDS EMERGE. WE NOW GO TO BALTIMORE, WHERE
JANET YELLEN, THE FED CHAIR, IS ABOUT TO BEGIN GIVING HER
COMMENCEMENT SPEECH. THE TOPIC IS ON THE STATE OF THE
LABOR MARKET. THE BRIGHT HEADLINES EARLIER
THAT INDICATED SHE DID NOT GIVE ANY INDICATION OF THE PATH OF
POLICY OR HER ECONOMIC OUTLOOK, BUT SHE DID MAKE COMMENTS ON THE
STATE OF THE LABOR MARKET, THING FOR THE MOST PART, THE LABOR
ECONOMY IS FAIRLY STRONG. I WILL BRING YOU THOSE
HEADLINES, RIGHT NOW. SHE SAID JOB CREATION IS
CONTINUING A STEADY PACE AND LAYOFFS ARE LOW.
ECONOMIC GAINS ARE FINALLY RAISING CLOSE TO LIVING
STANDARDS. SHE'S GETTING READY TO SPEAK AT
THE UNIVERSITY OF BALTIMORE'S MIDYEAR COMMENCEMENT CEREMONY.
WE'LL BRING YOU HER SPEECH WHEN IT BEGINS.
IN THE MEANTIME, LET'S BEGIN WITH HEADLINES IN THE BE -- IN
THE OIL MARKET. BP MAKES A TWO POINT $5 BILLION
DEAL. WE SPOKE TO BOB DUDLEY ABOUT THE
DEAL AND ASKED WHY IT HAS TAKEN SO LONG.
MR. DUDLEY: WE'VE BEEN WORKING HERE, ON IMPORTANT WORK THAT BP
HAS HAD FOR A LONG TIME WITH A STRATEGIC RELATIONSHIP.
TO BE HONEST, GIVEN OUR DISCIPLINED FINANCIAL FRAMEWORK,
IT TOOK US A WHILE TO WORK TO THE POINT WHERE WE COULD MAKE
THIS GREAT INVESTMENT WITH ABU DHABI AND THE KEY ELEMENT THERE
IS WE USED BP SHARES. ABU DHABI WILL OWN ABOUT 2% OF
BP. FOR BP, IT WILL MEAN ANOTHER
160,000 BARRELS A DAY, IN ADDITION TO THE 95,000 BARRELS A
DAY WE PRODUCE AND OPERA DOBBY. CONTINUING ON -- IN OPERA DOBBY
-- IN ABU DHABI. IT BRINGS IN A STRATEGIC OWNER
FOR THE COMPANY, AND BP HAS WORKED HERE FOR A LONG TIME.
WE HAVE SHOWN WE COULD DO TECHNICALLY WITH MANAGEMENT
CAPABILITY. WE WILL MOVE AND WORK WITH THEM
AND BRING OUR OWN BEST PEOPLE AND RESOURCES INTO IT TO HELP
MAXIMIZE FUTURE RECOVERIES OF THEIR RESOURCES.
WE HAVE A LOT OF EXPERIENCE OF WORKING AND MANAGING BIG OIL
FIELDS, LATE LIFE OIL FIELDS, WATER FLOODING IN THE TECHNICAL
THINGS WE WILL BRING. THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS WE
BRING GREAT AS A DEEP SENSE OF RESPONSIBILITY ABOUT THE
PRIVILEGE OF WORKING WITH THE NATURAL RESOURCES OF ABU DHABI.
&gt;&gt; SHOULD WE TAKE THIS DEAL AS A SIGN THAT NOW IS THE RIGHT TIME
FOR OIL MAJORS TO BEGIN RAMPING UP INVESTMENT?
&gt;&gt; ONE HAS TO HAVE SOME CONFIDENCE IN THE PRICE.
WE REALLY RETOOLED BP, GETTING DOWN TO AN EFFICIENT LEVEL.
WE SAID WE WOULD BALANCE OUR SOURCES OF FUNDS AT A $55 OIL
PRICE. A YEAR AGO, WE WERE SAYING $60,
NOW WE CAN DO AT $55. IT IS CLEARLY IN SIGHT.
I THINK WE REMAIN VERY DISCIPLINED ABOUT THE CAPITAL WE
SPEND IN THE PROJECT WE SELECT. IT'S TIME FOR BP TO START
GROWING. WE WORK THROUGH SO MANY
DIFFICULTIES IN THE U.S., THE COMPANY IS NOT WELL POSITIONED
TOWARDS GROWTH IN THE BEGINNING OF THE DECADE.
&gt;&gt; WE SAW AN HISTORIC DEAL FROM OPEC FOR THE PRODUCTION CUT AND
HISTORIC ONE BY NON-OPEC PRODUCERS TO JOIN IN WITH SOME
OF THOSE PRODUCTION CUTS. HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT OPEC AND THE
FUTURE OF OIL AT THE MOMENT? MR. DUDLEY: IT'S SIGNIFICANT
WHAT HAPPENED ON NOVEMBER 30. YOU HAVE NON-OPEC COUNTRIES
SERIES A TALKING ABOUT REDUCING THEIR OUTPUT.
SOME PEOPLE HAVE SAID THAT OPEC IS NOT A REAL ORGANIZATION
ANYMORE. IT DOESN'T ACTUALLY BRING THINGS
TOGETHER, AND I THINK OPEC IS AN IMPORTANT ORGANIZATION.
THIS AGREEMENT IS SIGNIFICANT. YOU CAN ALREADY SEE IT IN THE
CURTAILMENT OF US IS GOING OUT FOR THE MIDDLE EAST.
I KNOW, BECAUSE WE WORK IN RUSSIA, THERE'S A SCHEDULE OF
REDUCING OUTPUT FROM RUSSIA. I THINK IT'S VERY SERIOUS.
I THINK OIL PRICES BETWEEN $55 AND $60 A BARREL SEEMS VERY
REALISTIC FOR 2017. AND GROWTH CONTINUES IN CHINA
AND IN NORTH AMERICA. &gt;&gt; DONALD TRUMP HAS NOMINATED
REX TILLERSON IS A POTENTIAL SECRETARY OF STATE.
DO YOU THINK HE'S THE RIGHT MAN FOR THE JOB?
MR. DUDLEY: HE'S IN A CLUB PERSON WHO KNOWS THE WORLD, HE
KNOWS LEADERSHIP AROUND THE WORLD AND KNOWS HOW TO GET
THINGS DONE. HE'S A VERY SERIOUS PERSON.
I THINK HE WILL DO A GREAT JOB, NOT JUST BECAUSE I'M IN THE OIL
AND GAS INDUSTRY. US IS A MAN WHO REALLY KNOWS THE
WORLD AND KNOWS HOW TO MANAGE GLOBAL ORGANIZATIONS.
SCARLET: THAT WAS BP CEO BOB DUDLEY.
FED CHAIR JANET YELLEN HAS BEGUN SPEAKING AT THE UNIVERSITY OF
BALTIMORE. LET'S LISTEN IN, SHE TALKS ABOUT
AMERICAN LIVING STANDARDS RISING ECONOMIC GAINS.
CHAIR YELLEN: THERE ARE ALSO INDICATIONS THAT WAGE GROWTH IS
PICKING UP, AND WEEKLY EARNINGS FOR YOUNGER WORKERS HAVE MADE
STRONG GAINS OVER THE PAST COUPLE OF YEARS.
THAT IS PROBABLY ONE REASON WHY YOUNGER WORKERS REPORTED FEELING
SIGNIFICANTLY MORE OPTIMISTIC ABOUT THE JOB MARKET COMPARED
WITH 2013, ACCORDING TO A SURVEY PUBLISHED JUST TODAY BY THE
FEDERAL RESERVE. CHALLENGES DO REMAIN.
SCARLET: THAT WAS FED CHAIR JANET YELLEN.
YOU CAN WATCH THE REST OF HER REMARKS AT THE BLOOMBERG LIVE
GO. THIS IS BLOOMBERG.
♪ SCARLET: IT'S 2:00 P.M. IN NEW
YORK, AND 7:00 P.M., AND JULIE HYMAN.
OLIVER: AND I'M OLIVER RENICK. WELCOME TO "BLOOMBERG MARKETS."
JULIE: COVERING STORIES OUT OF WASHINGTON, IS SIMPLE, AND ABU
DHABI. A CAUTIOUS TONE TO THE MARKETS
TODAY, EXHAUSTED BY THE ASSASSINATION OF A RUSSIAN ENVOY
IN TURKEY'S CAPITAL. GOLD, THE YEN COME AND
TREASURIES CATCHING A BID AS INVESTORS LOOK FOR SAFETY.
ULTRALONG BONDS LOOK LIKE AN ULTRALONG SHOT, AT LEAST THAT'S
THE MESSAGE FROM STRATEGIST ABOUT STEVEN MNUCHIN'S IDEA OF A
50 YEAR OR 100 YEAR TREASURY. CHINESE LEADERS ARE BIDING THEIR
TONGUES AS TRUMP LASHES OUT OVER CHINA ABOUT -- AT BEIJING'S
RESPONSE WAS MUTED. U.S. MARKETS CLOSE IN TWO HOURS.
LET'S CHECK ON STOCKS WITH ABIGAIL DOOLITTLE.
ABIGAIL: STILL LOOKING AT GAINS. EVERYTHING TRADING HIGHER.
THE NASDAQ IS ON PACE FOR ANOTHER RECORD LOWS -- RECORD
CLOSE. THE DOW IS LESS THAN 15 POINTS,
12 POINTS WITH 13 POINTS AWAY FROM PERHAPS BEING ON PACE FOR
ITS OWN RECORD CLOSE. IT LITTLE BIT OF STRENGTH, BUT
TO DO IS POINT, WE ARE OFF THE HIGHS AND WE GOING TO THE
BLOOMBERG AND TAKE A LOOK AT THE IMAP FUNCTION FOR THE S&amp;P 500, A
GREAT FUNCTION TO SHOW WHAT THE SECTOR COMPOSITION, A QUICK
SNAPSHOT. WE SEE LOTS OF BREACHES, WE ALSO
SEE SOME RED HELPING THE NASDAQ OUTPERFORMS THE TECHNOLOGY
SECTOR, ONE OF THE TOP SECTORS. ON THE BOTTOM, WE HAD ENERGIES,
MATERIALS, AND FINANCIALS. YOU GO INTO THE MATERIALS OF
SPACE, WE HAVE SOME INTERESTING LETTERS INCLUDING MOSAIC, SHEARS
DOWN ABOUT 6% ON THE NEWS THAT THE COMPANY WILL BE BUYING A
FERTILIZER ASSET FOR $2.5 BILLION IN CASH AND STOCK.
THIS WILL GIVE THEM 11% STAKE IN MOSAIC, PLUS TWO SEATS ON THE
BOARD. WE ALSO HAVE FREEPORT MACK BROWN
DOWN ALMOST 3%, THIS IS THEIR SIXTH DOWN DAY IN A ROW, THE
LONGEST LOSING STREAK SINCE JANUARY OF LAST YEAR.
THIS IS COPPER IS DECLINING, DOWN FOR THE THIRD DAY IN A ROW.
HITTING LEVELS LAST SEEN RIGHT AROUND THE ELECTION.
A BIT OF A REVERSAL. AS FOR THE FINANCIALS, THIS IS
ANOTHER DRAG ON THE MARKET TODAY.
BANK OF AMERICA, WELLS FARGO, AND CITIGROUP ALL TRADING LOWER.
GUGGENHEIM SAID THEY SEE LIMITED UPSIDE AHEAD FOR BANKS,
FINANCIALS ARE AMONG ONE OF THE BEST SECTORS COMING OUT OF THE
ELECTION OF MORE THAN 50%. A BIT OF A BREATHER HERE.
ALSO PRESSURING THE BANKS TODAY ARE SAFE HAVEN ASSETS THAT JULIE
WAS MENTIONING, OR THE U.S. 10 YEAR YIELD BONDS.
WE TAKE A LOOK AT THESE HAVEN PLAYS, WE HAVE THE YEN TRADING
HIGHER, REPRESENTED HERE IN RED AGAINST THE DOLLAR VERSUS THE
YEN. THE YEN'S TRADING HIGHER COME
HAVEN CURRENCY. THE 10 YEAR YIELD DOWN FIVE
BASIS POINTS RIGHT NOW. PRICE DOES TRADE IN VERSE TWO
YIELD, SO BONDS GETTING A BIT OF A SAFE HAVEN BID, OR PERHAPS</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58582f07837ad70006f116ef_1</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1482176984279.1482174205481.9c79d857-8ba7-45df-b3be-aba9c306a9d5.segment1.thumb.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 19:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <segment:duration>861.493</segment:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Markets: European Close</title>
      <link>http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480429910203.4a1f9529-7fea-4efb-9cd8-873d0521067e.mp4#t=0.00,1367.76</link>
      <description>NOT NECESSARILY FUNDAMENTALS,
THAT HURTING METALS AS WELL. IN INDIVIDUAL MOVERS, WE DO HAVE
AN UPSIDE. BETTER SALES OUT OF U.S. AND
JAPAN. CARNIVAL, THAT STOCK OFF BY 15%.
LAST UP, THE STORE INDUSTRIES UP BY 10%.
RV MAKERS DID BY ARRIVAL EARLIER.
THESE STOCKS ON THE UPSIDE. DAVID: NUMBERS OUT OF A HOME
PRICES AND THEY ARE MILD DISAPPOINTMENT.
MONTH OVER MONTH THEY WENT UP .37%.
THE US WAS 2.4%. IT WAS EXPECTED TO BE 5.2% AND
THERE WAS A SLIGHT REVISION DOWNWARD FROM LAST MONTH.
IT WAS ORIGINALLY 5.13% AS OPPOSED TO 5.06.
EARLIER TODAY, ABOUT GDP RELIGIONS -- REVISIONS, ABOVE
WHAT WAS EXPECTED. WILL KENNEDY, MANAGING DIRECTOR
AND EDITOR FOR EUROPEAN AND MIDDLE EAST AND AFRICA
COMMODITIES JOINS US NOW FROM LONDON.
IT SEEMS LIKE EVERY MOMENT SOMEONE IS COMING OUT WITH SOME
STATEMENT ANOTHER. WHERE IS THE STATE OF PLAY?
&gt;&gt; WE'VE GOT THE OIL MINISTERS THEMSELVES.
THEY ARE ARRIVING IN THE ANNA AND WE SAW IN THE URANIAN -- THE
IRANIAN, THAT IS NOT A HUGE SUPPLY.
WHEN THEY CUT PRODUCTION THEY WANT ROOM TO INCREASE BUT THEY
ARE CLEARLY DIGGING THEIR HEELS IN.
SAUDI ARABIA NEED SOME KIND OF PARTICIPATION FOR IRAN AND IRAQ.
SOME KIND OF COMPROMISE ALLOWS SAUDI TO SAVE FACE AND IRAN TO
TAP PRODUCTION BUT NOT CUT IT. ALIX: ON THOSE HEADLINES, SAUDI
ARABIA SAYS THEY ARE READY TO REJECT THE DEAL UNLESS ALL OPEC
MEMBERS EXCEPT LIBYA AND NIGERIA PARTICIPATE.
THE ALGERIAN MINISTER SAYS, HEY, TALKS ARE PRETTY GOOD.
WE ARE MAKING PROGRESS. WHAT WOULD BE PROGRESS AT THIS
POINT? &gt;&gt; I THINK THE ALGERIAN TAKE IS
A LITTLE OPTIMISTIC. IT IS GOING TO COME DOWN TO THE
MEETING TOMORROW AT LUNCHTIME WHEN WE HAVE THEM SITTING
TOGETHER AND CAN THEY AGREE TO A LEVEL OF URANIUM PRODUCTION --
OF IRANIAN PRODUCTION THAT ALLOWS THEM TO CAP IT AND
SATISFY SAUDI DEMANDS. WE'VE GOT THE ROCK, WHICH IS
CONSISTENTLY CUTTING PRODUCTION, THAT IS PARTICIPATION AS WELL.
I THINK WE WILL WALK OUT OF TOMORROW'S MEETING WITH A DEAL
BUT WHAT THE SAUDI'S HAVE BEEN SAYING ALL WEEK IS THAT THEY ARE
NOT GOING TO DO ALL THE WORK. CARRY ON PUMPING.
ALIX: THAT LEADS US TO THE POTENTIAL DOWNSIDE.
YOU HAVE IT OFF BY 4% ENERGY ASPECTS BUT THE DOWNSIDE
POTENTIAL AND 20'S. WHAT ARE YOU HEARING?
&gt;&gt; WHAT WE HAVE SEEN TODAY IS PEOPLE ARE POSITIONING
THEMSELVES BECAUSE OF THIS CHANGE IN TONE, THIS BEARISH
SENTIMENT, WE ARE SEEING A LOT OF ACTIVITY IN THE OPTIONS
MARKET IF A DEAL DOESN'T HAPPEN SO WE COULD SEE A SELLOFF.
WHERE THAT ENDS THE FEWEST ONLINE WILL DEPEND ON THE
ASSUMPTION OF THE MARKET SHARE OR, AND THIS WILL BE REALLY
DISASTROUS FOR THE MARKET, PEOPLE START EDGING UP
PRODUCTION AGAIN. DAVID: WILL IS OUR MANAGING
EDITOR FOR EUROPE AND AFRICA. HE COVERS ENERGY AND
COMMODITIES. WE COULD SEE OIL PRICES FLY.
OIL IS MAYBE AS LOW AS $20. WHAT DOES IT MEAN FOR INVESTORS?
LISA SHALLOTS, WELCOME BACK TO THE PROGRAM.
WHAT ARE THE PRACTICAL EFFECT IF WE DO SEE OIL FALL BELOW THAT
$40 MARK? &gt;&gt; WE THINK IT IS CRITICAL THAT
WE GET A DEAL AND WE DO THINK WE ARE GOING TO GET ONE.
IF WE DON'T, GIVEN HOW QUICKLY RATES HAVE MOVED AND HOW STRONG
THE U.S. DOLLAR HAS GOTTEN, A VERY WEAK OIL PRICE WOULD
ACTUALLY HURT GLOBAL FINANCIAL CONDITIONS.
ONE YEAR AGO, WE HAD A STRONG DOLLAR AND THE FED RAISING RATES
IN DECEMBER AND OIL PRICES WERE VERY WEAK AND ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT CONSPIRED AGAINST MARKETS WERE THESE VERY TIGHT FINANCIAL
CONDITIONS. IF OIL PRICES ACTUALLY BREAKDOWN
INTO THE 30'S, WE COULD FIND OURSELVES IN A LITTLE BIT OF
THAT MARKET STRESS WE SAW LITERALLY ONE YEAR AGO.
IT IS PART OF THE THEME WE SEE IN THE LAST FEW WEEKS, IF YOU
HAVE OIL PRICES FALL, DOES THAT KILLED THE INFLATION THESIS? &gt;&gt;
I DON'T THINK IT KILL THE REFLATION PIECE.
LOW PRICES ARE GREAT FOR CONSUMERS BUT EMERGING MARKETS
REALLY DO NEED MORE STABLE OIL PRICES.
I THINK THE SAUDI'S ARE GOING TO "MAKE IT HAPPEN."
DAVID: YOU SET UP THESE PORTFOLIOS.
THERE IS NO ONE FACTOR BUT IF YOU TAKE ONE, DOES IT MEAN IT IS
GOOD FOR BONDS AND THAT FOR EQUITIES?
&gt;&gt; IF WE COULD GO RISK OFF, YOU DON'T GET AN OIL DEAL BECAUSE
OIL COULD REALLY EXACERBATE THAT STRENGTHENING OF THE DOLLAR IF
OIL PRICES CRASH THROUGH THAT $40 MARK.
WHEN WE HAVE A STRONG DOLLAR OR A STRONG DOLLAR TOO QUICKLY,
THAT COULD HURT S&amp;P 500 PROFITS. DAVID: YOU ARE EXPECTING A DEAL
OF SOME SORT. SO WE ARE GOING TO HAVE A $30
OIL. IN THE WAKE OF DONALD TRUMP
SELECTION, IT IS FAIR TO SAY, HOW REAL IS THAT?
&gt;&gt; I THINK WE UNDERSTAND THE SENTIMENT HAS CLEARLY CHANGED
WITH THE SURPRISE OUTCOME OF THE ELECTION BUT WHAT WE HAVE REALLY
BEEN FOCUSED ON IS THE FUNDAMENTALS.
WE SAW THIS MORNING THAT U.S. GDP WAS ACTUALLY REVISED HIGHER
AND SINCE OCTOBER, WE HAVE SEEN A STRENGTHENING IN OVERALL
ECONOMIC DATA AND THAT HAS REALLY BEEN WHAT IS DRIVING THE
S&amp;P 500 EARNINGS ESTIMATE HIGHER.
ONE OF THE THINGS WE FOCUSEDONE, WE WERE LOOKING AT AN S&amp;P 500
EARNINGS PER SHARE OF ABOUT ONE DOLLAR 20 -- 120, 125 OR NOW IS
MOVING 130, 1 35 WHICH SUPPORTS 2300 ON THE S&amp;P 500.
ALIX: YES, WE'VE GOT THE BEST GDP GROWTH SINCE 2014, WE ARE
ALSO GETTING A STRONGER DOLLAR ON THE BACK OF THAT, WHAT POINT
DOES THAT CYCLE THROUGH FINANCIAL CONDITIONS?
&gt;&gt; IT HAS BUT IT HAS NOT BEEN WHAT WE SAW A YEAR AGO.
IT IS BECAUSE OF THIS OIL BEING SPLASHED IN.
IF WE GET A VERY STRONG DOLLAR IN VERY WEAK OIL, THAT
COMBINATION -- WHICH WE HAVEN'T HAD IN THIS LAST THREE OR FOUR
WEEKS -- OIL HAS BEEN RANGE BOUND -- THAT COULD BREAK THINGS
AND THOUGHT THIS RALLY OUT -- AND THAW THIS RALLY OUT.
ALIX: NOW FOR AN UPDATE ON NEWS OUTSIDE THE BUSINESS WORLD, WE
GO TO EMMA CHANDRA. &gt;&gt; IN COLUMBIA AUTHORITIES ARE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHY A CHARTER JET CARRYING A BRAZILIAN
SOCCER TEAM CRASHED INTO A MOUNTAINSIDE.
FIVE OF THE 81 ON BOARD SURVIVED.
IT WAS CARRYING A PROFESSIONAL TEAM TO GAME IN THE CITY.
THE CREW DECLARED AN EMERGENCY. INVESTIGATORS ARE LOOKING INTO
AN ACCOUNT FROM ONE OF THE SURVIVORS THAT THE PLANE RAN OUT
OF FUEL. GOVERNMENT OFFICERS IN CUBA WILL
BE CLEARED FOR A SECOND DAY OF MEMORIAL.
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF CUBANS HAVE BEEN BIDDING FAREWELL TO
THEIR FORMER LEADER AND PLEDGING ALLEGIANCE TO HIS IDEOLOGY.
DONALD TRUMP BURNING THE U.S. FLAG SHOULD BE ILLEGAL.
IN AN EARLY-MORNING TWEET HE SAID "NOBODY SHOULD BE ALLOWED
TO BURN THE AMERICAN FLAG. IF THERE DO -- IF THEY DO, THEY
SHOULD BE CONSEQUENCES." THE SUPREME COURT RULED THAT IT
IS A FORM OF POLITICAL EXPRESSION.
GLOBAL NEWS, 24 HOURS A DAY, POWERED BY MORE THAN 2600
JOURNALISTS AND ANALYSTS IN MORE THAN 120 COUNTRIES.
THIS IS BLOOMBERG. ALIX: WE DO WANT TO FOLLOW WHAT
IS HAPPENING WITH OIL. PRICES OFF BY THREE AND A HALF
PERCENT. NOW SLIPPING INTO NEGATIVE
TERRITORY FOR THIS SESSION. HERE ARE THE HEADLINES THAT
CAUGHT EVERYONE'S I. IRANIAN OIL MINISTER SAYS THEY
WILL NOT TOUCH PRODUCTION. THEY WILL ONLY ACCEPT EXEMPTIONS
FROM NIGERIA AND LIBYA. THEY ARE READY TO REJECT THE
DEAL IF IRAN AND IRAQ DO NOT PARTICIPATE.
DAVID: WE HAVE A BUMPY 24 HOURS AHEAD.
EVERY MINUTE, THINGS CAN CHANGE. JOIN US NEXT IS CHRIS AILMAN,
OWNER OF THE LARGEST PENSION FUND.
WHAT IS HIS STRATEGY TO FIND YIELDS?
THIS IS BLOOMBERG. &gt;&gt; IN THE TWO WEEKS SINCE DONALD
TRUMP'S VICTORY, INVESTORS HAVE PULLED $10 MILLION IN U.S. BOND
FUNDS. IS THE WORST OF THE ROUTE OVER
OR IS THERE MORE TO COME? JOINING US NOW IS CHRIS AILMAN,
CEO OF THE BIGGEST PENSION FUND IN THE U.S., AND WITH US IS
LISA SHALLOTS. IS THE 30 YEAR BOND MARKET OVER?
I THINK IT IS &gt;&gt;. &gt;&gt; I SAID THAT ABOUT THREE YEARS
AGO AT THE CONFERENCE AND WAS DEAD WRONG.
THAT LONG-TERM CHANNEL WE HAVE BEEN IN, I THINK THAT WE ARE
STARTING TO SEE IT HAD TOWARDS BREAKING IN THE UPSIDE.
I THINK THE LONG-TERM ROUTE IS OVER.
DAVID: WE ARE GOING TO HAVE A PRESIDENT AND  HOUSE AND
SENATE ALL OF THE SAME PARTY. &gt;&gt; IT MIGHT LEAD TO SOME LEVEL
OF INFLATION. THE WORLD IS MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT GLOBAL  DEFLATION BEFORE THIS.
WE ARE GOING TO BREAK OUT ON THE UPSIDE WHICH IS THAT FOR BOND
INVESTMENTS. &gt;&gt; IF WE ARE CREDITING
EVERYTHING TO THIS TRUMP WIN, -- THIS IS MY FAVORITE CHART OF THE
DAY -- THIS IS A BOND AND EQUITY VOLUME.
IF THIS REALLY WAS A MACRO PICTURE THEY SHOULD BE HIGHLY
CORRELATED. &gt;&gt; I THINK AS WE TALKED ABOUT
BEFORE THE BREAK, CLEARLY, TRUMP IS DRIVING SENTIMENT BUT THE
FUNDAMENTALS ARE STILL DRIVING THE BUS.
THE FUNDAMENTALS HAVE BEEN MUCH MUCH BETTER IN TERMS OF ECONOMIC
GROWTH AS WE SAW WITH THE GDP NUMBERS.
YOU SEE IN THE LAST COUPLE OF WEEKS, AT A RETAIL SALES.
HOUSING STARTS. THIS IS AN ECONOMY THAT IS
SLOWLY BUT SURELY POWERING FORWARD AND QUITE FRANKLY, THE
INFLATION DATA IS -- AGAIN -- IN A VERY LOPEZ INCHING TOWARDS
THAT 2% ON TARGET. WE DO BELIEVE THAT THE
UNDERLYING ECONOMY IS NORMALIZING AND YOU ARE STARTING
TO SEE MARKETS NORMALIZE ALONG WITH IT.
&gt;&gt; IN THE LAST FEW WEEKS, THE MARKET REACTION IS BASICALLY TWO
YEARS WITH JANET YELLEN'S TIGHTENING.
NOW, WE HAVE GOTTEN THAT PRICED IN WHICH I HAVE BEEN ARGUING FOR
YEARS -- WE NEED TO GET BACK TO NORMAL INTEREST RATES EVEN IF IT
IS JUST 3%. &gt;&gt; AS LISA POINTS OUT, INFLATION
DATA WAS STARTED AT JUST FOUR DOLLARS.
BUT MY QUESTION IS, IS THAT TRUE IN EUROPE AND ASIA?
WE SEEING DIVERGENCE IN TERMS OF THE ECONOMY.
&gt;&gt; WE THOUGHT THAT WAS GOING TO BE A CENTRAL BANK DIVERGENCE
LAST YEAR BUT NOW WE ARE COMING BACK TO WHERE WE WILL BE
TIGHTENING. I CAN'T FORECAST WHAT THE UK'S
GOING TO DO BUT THE U.K. AND ASIA HAVE TO STIMULATE THAT
ECONOMY. WITH OPEC IN CHAOS WE ARE NOT
SURE WHAT WILL HAPPEN. ALL I AM SAYING IS INFLATION IS
GOING TO BE HIGH BUT IT IS GOING TO GET OFF THE FLOOR AT LEAST
FROM ZERO TO TWO, WHICH WOULD BE HELPFUL FOR THE ECONOMY AND
CHANGE OF THE RECEPTION FOR LONG-TERM INVESTMENTS.
ALIX: HOW DO YOU PLACE CENTRAL BANK DIVERGENCE?
&gt;&gt; I THINK WHAT WE WOULD SAY IS THAT WHAT WE WANT TO DO IS HAVE
A GLOBAL PORTFOLIO. BECAUSE ONE OF THE THINGS --
WHILE WE LOVE THE U.S. WE NEED TO BE VERY CAREFUL THAT WE ARE
IN THE EIGHTH YEAR OF U.S. EQUITIES OUTPERFORMING THE REST
OF THE WORLD. THE U.S. DOLLAR IS BEGINNING TO
MEANINGFULLY REFLECT THAT FACT. IT CONTINUES TO STRENGTHEN AND
THESE WEAKER CURRENCIES OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES ARE GOING TO
HELP SOME OF THESE ECONOMIES. IN EUROPE, WE JUST START TO SEE
OUR FIRST POSITIVE INFLECTION IN EARNINGS.
EUROPEAN COMPANY EARNINGS FOR THE FIRST TIME IN FIVE YEARS.
WE ARE HOPING FOR SOME HOPEFUL NEWS OUT OF JAPAN.
SO WE ARE ENCOURAGING OUR CLIENTS TO GLOBALIZE.
IT IS EASY TO FALL IN LOVE WITH THE U.S..
WE ALL HAVE A HOME COUNTRY BIAS BUT WE THINK THERE ARE
OPPORTUNITIES IN 2017 OUTSIDE THE U.S..
&gt;&gt; IT IS CURRENCY, CURRENCY, CURRENCY.
THAT HAS BEEN THE VOLATILITY STORY AND IT IS GOING TO BE
GOING FORWARD ON AN INFINITE RISE BOND YIELD.
PUT THIS IN YOUR POCKET. LOOK AT SOME OF THE CURRENCIES.
IT REALLY IS OFF THE CHART. MOST OF THE INVESTORS WATCHING
THIS SHOW, WE HAVE A HOME COUNTRY BIAS TO THE U.S.
CANADIANS ARE HAVING A HUGE IMPACT ON THEM AND IF YOU ARE IN
EUROPE OR A NATION BASED FUND YOU HAVE TO PAY ATTENTION.
DAVID: WHAT MORE COULD YOU WANT THEM CHRIS ALEMAN DOING YOUR
WORK FOR YOU? &gt;&gt; THANK YOU.
DAVID: THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING WITH US.
STILL AHEAD, MORE WITH CHRIS AILMAN ON WHERE HE IS FINDING
RETURNS. THAT IS NEXT AND THIS IS
BLOOMBERG. ALIX: CONTINUING TO TRACK THESE
BREAKING OPEC HEADLINES, CRUDE OIL IS DOWN.
SOME ARE TRYING TO TALK IT UP. MAKING THE MEETING SUCCESSFUL,
THE UAE MINISTER SAYS HE IS OPTIMISTIC BUT IRAN IS REALLY
PUTTING THE SPIRIT IN THAT SAYING THEY WOULD NOT BE CUTTING
PRODUCTION. THE SAUDI'S SAY THEY WILL NOT
CUT WITHOUT IRAN AND IRAQ DAVID: .
YOU COULD PUT THIS IN PRIMETIME. NOW WE ARE GOING BACK TO PENSION
PLANS. EARNING 1.4%.
THAT IS THE SECOND CONSECUTIVE YEAR.
IN AN INTERVIEW IN OCTOBER -- THIS IS UNFAIR BECAUSE IT'S
BEFORE THE ELECTION -- CHRIS ALEMAN -- CHRIS AILMAN SAYS "WE
THINK YOU WILL SEE RETURNS AND A LOT OF ACCEPT CLASSES -- ASSET
CLASSES." DAVID: DO YOU WANT TO AMEND YOUR
STATEMENT? &gt;&gt; I DO BUT NOT JUST BECAUSE OF
DONALD TRUMP. IT IS MORE OF THE BOND MARKET
REACTION AND THE FACT THAT WE ARE GOING TO HAVE, POTENTIALLY,
WITH A DIFFERENT WHITE HOUSE AND A DIFFERENT CONGRESS, A
DIFFERENT PLAN IN THE U.S. AND IN THE GLOBE.
AFTER JIM, EVERYTHING CHANGED AFTER BREXIT.
REMEMBER JULY, HERE WE ARE ALMOST SIX MONTHS LATER AND WE
DON'T KNOW WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN IN EUROPE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENS IN THE USA EVEN SIX MONTHS FROM NOW.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT ACTIONS IN WASHINGTON DC.
IT IS GOING TO LEAVE INVESTMENT OPPORTUNITIES.
WE COULD EASILY GET A 7-8% RETURN ON THAT EQUITY.
WE ARE GOING TO SEE SOME LONG-TERM INVESTMENTS,
PARTICULARLY PRIVATE EQUITY AND INFRASTRUCTURE CAN BE AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR LONG-TERM INVESTMENT.
DAVID: BREXIT WAS A RISK SITUATION.
THIS APPEARS TO BE A RISK ON SITUATION WHICH APPEARS TO DRIVE
UP EQUITIES. DOES THAT CHANGE YOUR INVESTMENT
STRATEGY?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">583d91c8a47c5300012e2414_0</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480433155684.1480429910203.4a1f9529-7fea-4efb-9cd8-873d0521067e.segment0.thumb.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <segment:duration>1367.757</segment:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Markets: European Close</title>
      <link>http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480429910203.4a1f9529-7fea-4efb-9cd8-873d0521067e.mp4#t=1367.76,1797.09</link>
      <description>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; IT DOES NOT CHANGE OUR
INVESTMENT STRATEGY. WE HAVE A 10 TO 20 YEAR
INVESTMENT HORIZON AND I WOULD ENCOURAGE ANYONE OUT THERE WITH
A 401(K), YOU DON'T WANT TO MAKE WILD CHANGES.
BUT WE HAVE A LONG-TERM ASSET ALLOCATION.
ALL THIS DOES IS CHANGE OUR REBALANCING POLICY.
WE NEED TO CREATE LIQUIDITY, HOW QUICKLY AND WHAT DO WE SELL.
IN THE EMERGING MARKETS, WE ARE SLOWING THAT DOWN.
WE ARE JUST SLOWING DOWN OUR PURCHASING AND MOVING AWAY FROM
THE HOME COUNTRY BIAS. THAT WAS OUR LONG-TERM PLAN.
DAVID: SO THE REBALANCING, YOU ARE LOOKING AT IT AS MORE
GEOGRAPHICAL THAN ASSET LASSES. -- ASSET CLASSES.
&gt;&gt; WITHIN ASSET CLASSES WE ARE PRIMARILY LAUNCHED FROM
INVESTMENTS. WE HAVE REAL ESTATE IN THE USA
FOR THE PAST YEAR AND WE WILL CONTINUE FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF
YEARS IN TERMS OF STILL BUYING COLLECTIVELY BUT SELLING MORE
THAN WE ARE BUYING. IN LONG-TERM INVESTORS, WE ARE
INVESTING MORE THERE AND REDUCING THAT PORTFOLIO.
DAVID: AS A LONG-TERM INVESTOR, IT DOESN'T NECESSARILY HURT YOU
BECAUSE YOU ARE HOLDING FOR THE DURATION.
WE HAVE A LONG BOND IN TERMS OF A RISK HEDGE.
YOU HAVE SOME DECLINES IN THAT BUT WE ARE STILL GOING TO HOLD
AND NOT SELL IT. IF WE COULD GET BACK TO
SOMETHING LIKE NORMAL INTEREST RATES, THAT IS GOOD FOR
LONG-TERM INVESTMENTS. DAVID: THAT WOULD BE GOOD FOR
YOU. CHRIS AILMAN, WE WILL BE STAYING
WITH YOU THROUGH THE MARKET OPEN.
ALIX: PERFORMANCE AWAY FROM THE OPENING BELL, U.S. FUTURES HAVE
GIVEN UP THEIR DAYS. UNABLE TO RESIST THE LURE OF
LOWER OIL. DAVID: THIS IS BLOOMBERG
DAYBREAK. WE ARE A LITTLE UNDER 30 SECONDS
FROM THE OPENING BELL. LET'S LOOK AT THE FUTURES RIGHT
NOW. DOW JONES AND S&amp;P FUTURES, EVEN
AS WE WATCH, THERE IS A LITTLE BIT OF A CHANGE.
THIS IS ACTUALLY AN IMPORTANT POINT.
NEWS OF WHAT IS GOING ON IN VIENNA, OIL WENT DOWN TO NEW
LOWS AND IT HAS TAKEN MARKETS BACK.
LET'S LOOK AT OTHER ASSET CLASSES.
WEAKER SLIGHTLY, THAT IS A CONTINUATION OF THE PATTERNS
SINCE THE DONALD TRUMP ELECTION. THIS IS THE BIG STORY.
CRUDE DOWN. ARE THEY GOING TO HAVE A DEAL OR
NOT? APPARENTLY, A STATEMENT IS
COMING OUT OF IRAN. WE WILL FIND OUT WHAT IS REALLY
GOING ON IN THE MARKETS. ALIX: HERE IS WHERE WE ARE
STACKING UP, FLAT ACROSS THE BOARD WITH THE NASDAQ EKING OUT
A SLIGHT GAIN. S&amp;P RELATIVELY UP.
IT IS REALLY ABOUT OIL. S&amp;P  NOT ABLE TO HOLD
ONTO EARLIER GAINS. HAVING ITS WORST DAY SINCE JULY,
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT IT MEANS FOR ENERGY STOCKS.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT OIL HERE. EXXON OFF BY 1%.
THE OIL SERVICES COMPANY OFF BY MORE THAN 2%.
THE SAUDI'S SAY THEY WILL NOT ADHERE TO A DEAL IF IRAN AND
IRAQ DO NOT PARTICIPATE AND YOU HAVE  -- YOU WILL HAVE IRAQ
AND THE OTHER SYRIAN OIL MINISTER.
THE MARKET IS REALLY ZONING IN ON IRAN AND WHAT THE SAUDI'S ARE
SAYING. DAVID?
DAVID: TELSTRA'S HAS BEEN A</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">583d91c8a47c5300012e2414_1</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://um-bubble.media.mit.edu:10022/static/1480433267407.1480429910203.4a1f9529-7fea-4efb-9cd8-873d0521067e.segment1.thumb.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <segment:duration>429.328</segment:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
